[Music]
Welcome back to Profitable
Funds. Today, we're talking to
Sanjay Bambalkar of Union AMC,
trying to understand
why someone should invest in Union's Multicap Fund.
You've had a lot of exposure to insurance as a sector,
and a little exposure to general insurance as well.
My question is, isn't the life
insurance sector very
predictable? Because
people know the pie, so
by extrapolating it, we can understand
how growth can happen in life insurance,
so why is it so high in life insurance?
Especially for the big, biggest
life insurance companies,
Neeraj ji, we go through a process of stock
selection and construction.
In this process, good companies with
good growth potential are selected. And
portfolio construction is done through a quantum approach.
So, insurance
companies are very good in the Aarohi Aarushi
profile today. Well, today they are going fast.
We feel that their address market
is currently very low due to low penetration.  It
is huge, there can be huge growth going forward. If
you do a global comparison in insurance penetration also, then
you will see our insurance at 14-15 in global comparison, depending on the country in which
you are
looking. So we feel that
insurance companies are getting a huge runway.
Many people in India have also seen that there is a
need for insurance, so we feel
that insurance is an alternative
for individuals and it seems to be coming in the future,
so insurance is
also good,
their valuation has also been corrected, that is why
we like insurance companies.
Sir, there is a lot of discussion about two sectors
for today, so now people are taking a little contract in it,
they feel that the
item has bottomed out a lot, going forward from here there will be a
good boom in it, your
exposure is decent, in this
you have the second biggest, it is more than 6%
and there is a
lot of discussion in this also with a difference,
man and
expectedly the government allocations are also
increasing in this, so first of all, are you  Do
you agree that the
bottom has been formed in IT and the boom will increase?
If you agree, will you
increase exposure to it? Our
IT companies have provided
very good wealth creation for investors in the last
20 years. In the last two and a half years,
IT growth was also very good, particularly after the
provided
period, IT growth has accelerated. But this
environment of growth slowdown that is going on right now,
global growth has become such that
IT growth may also decrease
because as the development economy slows down,
IT growth may decrease. It may
impact online
banks or their
eight to nine percent of the top line has been formed. So
a question was arising there that it will happen in the middle
and its major impact will be on the IT company
that actually this company is
global CR efficient, global
cheap capital, cheap oil, these two Rabis
seem to be ending and in India still
access to labor is quite available, see
think debt and  Most of the tilleparas are also
available and that is why the Indian IT companies are in a very good
position. In the last two-three
quarters, you will see that the order books of the IT companies have
come, the
resilience they have shown,
keeping that in mind, the future of the IT companies seems to be getting even better. So,
we
feel that the IT company should be in our portfolio
and accordingly, we should
select the IT company
in the defense sector.
You know that there are so many
dependencies here that we cannot have on others.
In fact, India is becoming a defense
export destination. There are many
good companies which have
technology and order books.
Their profile of Aarohi Aro is also good. So,
we are very positive in that defense company.
One more thing, Sir, you have included many companies in retail as well, and there are
premium companies as well as meat products companies.
Now, this is a very strange time. At
this time, there is a lot of sale in the premium sector
and the meat product companies are facing a
lot of problems. So,
some thought will be given in this that you should make a change.
You will see that a bit of an environment is being created
for India. The
inflation rate in Madras city is very high, and the price
of Madras is high, and its
impact seems to be
more on the particular bottom of the pyramid consumer. So,
we feel
that until this environment improves a bit,
premium consumers, for whom a
little bit of inflation impact does
not make much difference, and those who are
from the sector, they are off.
Absolutely, Sanjay ji, it was a lot of fun. You
spoke very interestingly and you spoke with a lot of clarity. The
promise of this show is that
we try to read the mind of the fund manager.
For those
viewers who want to watch this show and invest,
how our fund manager will
run our fund, how much clarity is there
in his mind about the market, so
very good interviews, you talked interestingly,
thank you very much for joining us.
And those who are watching this show, you
can consider it. We have asked many questions and
discussed all the sectors, so you can think about
investing on this.  I can think about it,
you can get more opinions from me, finish
your advice, thank you very much sir,
thank you for joining us
[music]